[{"answer": "It's unlike anything I've ever covered before.", "docId": "130313pmt", "aSentId": 31, "question": "What was it like?", "qSentId": 30}, {"answer": "Well, you know, it's interesting.", "docId": "130313pmt", "aSentId": 58, "question": "Why do you think they did that and why him?", "qSentId": 57}, {"answer": "He's -- they have a schedule for him that's set out the next few days that has with him having mass tomorrow in a discreet way, and he'll start to build towards more public appearances.", "docId": "130313pmt", "aSentId": 86, "question": "When does he give his first mass and so on?", "qSentId": 85}, {"answer": "Totally significant.", "docId": "130313pmt", "aSentId": 121, "question": "How significant is that choice of name?", "qSentId": 120}, {"answer": "Well, first of all, I think if there is a great sense of relief that they're not the Pope.", "docId": "130313pmt", "aSentId": 144, "question": "What is the general reaction, do you think, from the cardinals who have elected this man?", "qSentId": 143}, {"answer": "Well, you know, I think what we're talking about here is a man who is very much, as every one of the 115 cardinals, is an orthodox man.", "docId": "130313pmt", "aSentId": 185, "question": "And what do you imagine his idea of reformation may be?", "qSentId": 184}, {"answer": "ANTORUM: He is, in my -- I would not call him a progressive conservative.", "docId": "130313pmt", "aSentId": 206, "question": "Is that the kind of person, do you think, that the Catholic Church needs?", "qSentId": 205}, {"answer": "I have no doubt that this is a man who, as you heard talk about, is very much committed to doing the right thing, to standing up for the truth and for making sure that people are held to account, and to holiness, I think, a couple of your commentators said.", "docId": "130313pmt", "aSentId": 225, "question": "Do you think he's going to go after this?", "qSentId": 224}, {"answer": "Well, I'm not going to -- I'm not going to make this judgment until I hear the rationale for, you know, the theological rationale and underpinning as to why that is a morally right thing to do.", "docId": "130313pmt", "aSentId": 238, "question": "Could you see yourself supporting that if he said that?", "qSentId": 237}, {"answer": "Well, the most important thing is to save souls.", "docId": "130313pmt", "aSentId": 251, "question": "And that surely in the end is a Christian answer, isn't it?", "qSentId": 250}, {"answer": "I don't think that we can expect from Pope Francis any move along the lines you were just suggesting.", "docId": "130313pmt", "aSentId": 270, "question": "What is your view about changing times, changing moods amongst -- certainly young Catholics?", "qSentId": 269}, {"answer": "There is none that I know.", "docId": "130313pmt", "aSentId": 337, "question": "What is your belief?", "qSentId": 336}, {"answer": "I think the most important thing is his personal credibility.", "docId": "130313pmt", "aSentId": 353, "question": "Is he going to move, do you think, on any of these key things?", "qSentId": 352}, {"answer": "I doubt it, Piers, exactly for the reason that you're mentioning.", "docId": "130313pmt", "aSentId": 377, "question": "But could it be a problem later in his life?", "qSentId": 376}, {"answer": "Well, age isn't measured in years as much anymore, Piers, as you know.", "docId": "130313pmt", "aSentId": 397, "question": "Are you surprised that they went for somebody of that age, or not really?", "qSentId": 396}, {"answer": "I'm doing well.", "docId": "130313pmt", "aSentId": 415, "question": "Mr. Speaker, how are you?", "qSentId": 414}, {"answer": "Well, I think the fact that he became Pope Francis is extraordinarily important.", "docId": "130313pmt", "aSentId": 419, "question": "What is your immediate gut reaction to this appointment of Pope Francis?", "qSentId": 418}, {"answer": "Look, I'm going to go out on a limb for a second.", "docId": "130313pmt", "aSentId": 436, "question": "Has that given him a taste, do you think of, what battles may be to come?", "qSentId": 435}, {"answer": "Listen, with great respect, Mr. Speaker -- we're going to take a quick break.", "docId": "130313pmt", "aSentId": 451, "question": "I mean, if we would just -- you know, in the middle of all of the elites' angst about their personal lives, if we could just look at it for a second and say, won't it be amazing to have a Pope who genuinely focusing, in the tradition of Saint Francis, on helping the poorest among us?", "qSentId": 450}, {"answer": "I can't believe you used that word on evening television.", "docId": "130313pmt", "aSentId": 516, "question": "Have you made up with him?", "qSentId": 515}, {"answer": "I wasn't worried about me.", "docId": "130313pmt", "aSentId": 520, "question": "Were you offended by that?", "qSentId": 519}, {"answer": "Look, I have no idea what he said to a reporter who reported all that.", "docId": "130313pmt", "aSentId": 525, "question": "But are you best buddies again with Roger Ailes?", "qSentId": 524}, {"answer": "No.", "docId": "130313pmt", "aSentId": 538, "question": "But are you seriously going to do this?", "qSentId": 537}]